<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://sylvansun.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://sylvansun.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2023-08-15T07:03:20+00:00</updated><id>https://sylvansun.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Homepage of Yilin Sun</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">(WIP) My recommendations for Japanese detective fictions</title><link href="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/jp-detective-fictions-recommendation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="(WIP) My recommendations for Japanese detective fictions"/><published>2023-08-14T12:02:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-08-14T12:02:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/jp-detective-fictions-recommendation</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/jp-detective-fictions-recommendation/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="try-crane-of-the-north-if-not-knowing-where-to-start">Try <em>Crane of the North</em> if not knowing where to start</h2> <h1 id="soji-shimada">Soji Shimada</h1> <h2 id="the-widely-acknowledged-top-5">The widely acknowledged top 5</h2> <h3 id="the-tokyo-zodiac-murders">The Tokyo Zodiac Murders</h3> <h3 id="murder-in-the-crooked-mansion">Murder in the Crooked Mansion</h3> <h3 id="the-knight-stranger">The Knight Stranger</h3> <h3 id="kiso-ten-o-ugokasu">Kiso, Ten o Ugokasu</h3> <h2 id="if-you-are-interested-in-the-relationship-between-takeshi-and-michiko">If you are interested in the relationship between Takeshi and Michiko</h2> <h3 id="hagoromo-densetsu-no-kioku">Hagoromo Densetsu no Kioku</h3> <h1 id="keigo-higashino">Keigo Higashino</h1> <h2 id="the-best-books-of-higashino-are-in-diversed-styles">The best books of Higashino are in diversed styles</h2> <h3 id="malice">Malice</h3> <h3 id="after-school">After School</h3> <h3 id="the-devotion-of-suspect-x">The Devotion of Suspect X</h3> <h3 id="journey-under-the-midnight-sun">Journey Under the Midnight Sun</h3> <h2 id="other-books-worth-reading">Other books worth reading</h2> <h3 id="the-bonds-of-the-shooting-star">The Bonds of the Shooting Star</h3> <h3 id="miracles-of-the-namiya-general-store">Miracles of the Namiya General Store</h3> <h3 id="the-street-where-the-dawn-breaks">The Street Where the Dawn Breaks</h3> <h3 id="naoko">Naoko</h3> <h1 id="miyuki-miyabe">Miyuki Miyabe</h1> <h3 id="all-she-was-worth">All She Was Worth</h3> <h3 id="the-reason">The Reason</h3> <h3 id="the-copycat">The Copycat</h3> <h3 id="solomons-perjury">Solomon’s Perjury</h3> <h1 id="others">Others</h1> <h2 id="assorted-books">Assorted Books</h2> <h3 id="points-and-lines">Points and Lines</h3> <h3 id="klein-bottle">Klein Bottle</h3> <h2 id="assorted-writers">Assorted Writers</h2> <h3 id="seishi-yokomizo">Seishi Yokomizo</h3> <h3 id="seiichirou-oyama">Seiichirou Oyama</h3> <h3 id="masahiro-imamura">Masahiro Imamura</h3> <h3 id="yukito-ayatsuji">Yukito Ayatsuji</h3>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="reviews"/><category term="books"/><category term="fictions"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Try Crane of the North if not knowing where to start]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I took the 16 personalities test and got ISFJ-T again</title><link href="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/personality-test/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I took the 16 personalities test and got ISFJ-T again"/><published>2023-08-13T15:10:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-08-13T15:10:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/personality-test</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/personality-test/"><![CDATA[<p>I took the 16 personalities test again and got the same result as last time. I’m again classified as an ISFJ-T, or a Turbulent Defender. Previously I did not believe these kind of tests considering that their questions are too vague and the results are too general, but I decide to record the results and do it again next year for further comparison.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 480px)" srcset="/assets/img/16personalities/history230813-480.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 800px)" srcset="/assets/img/16personalities/history230813-800.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 1400px)" srcset="/assets/img/16personalities/history230813-1400.webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/16personalities/history230813.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="auto" height="auto" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> Test history. </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="profile"/><category term="personality"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm starting to believe the test results seeing how consistent they are...]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">So I went to see MI:7 Dead Reckoning Part 1…</title><link href="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/MI7-dead-reckoning-p1/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="So I went to see MI:7 Dead Reckoning Part 1…"/><published>2023-08-08T15:12:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-08-08T15:12:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/MI7-dead-reckoning-p1</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/MI7-dead-reckoning-p1/"><![CDATA[<h3 id="spoiler-alert">Spoiler Alert</h3> <p>I went to see Tom Cruise’s latest Mission Impossible series movie, Dead Reckoning(Part 1), as soon as it was released in China last month. The movie is worth watching for the action scenes alone, yet I was a little bit unsatisfied with their arrangement of Ilsa’s ending. More precisely, I convinced myself to calm down with the hope of her death as an approach of deceiving the artificial intelligence. Should her death become a reality, I will definitely be furious.</p> <p>Getting back to the point, when asked about your film-viewing experience about an MI series movie, one’s impressions are typically classified into two categories: scene and plot. Considering that almost a month has passed since I watched the movie, the remaining memories are impressive and worth discussion.</p> <h2 id="plots">Plots</h2> <h3 id="the-tightly-knit-mi-trio">The tightly knit MI trio</h3> <p>The footage is well distributed among the actors, with Ethan being the point man, Luther the reliable technician, and Benji the comic relief. The trio is a well-oiled machine, with each member playing their part to perfection. For me one of the most important driver that keeps me coming back to the theater over and over again is the chemistry between the three. I always treasure friendship and the interpretation of camaraderie in MI series is way better than that in other movies of the same genre(no offense).</p> <p>Ever since they arranged the plot of Ethan saving Benji at the risk of giving huge amount of untracable money to Lane at the end of MI:5 and Ethan saving Luther with the danger of lossing the plutonium at the start of MI:6, I have known that no crisis can make them turn their backs on each other. Should there be any substitution of any single member of the team, I will not buy it. With this premise in mind, my doubt about Ilsa’s ending arose quite naturally.</p> <h3 id="ilsas-endingperhaps">Ilsa’s ending(perhaps?)</h3> <p>Frankly speaking, I did not expect that Ilsa would die at all when Gabriel announced that one of Ilsa and Grace would be killed so that the chance of him acquiring the key would be the highest under the prediction of AI. After all, we are talking about the female agent who was capable of carrying out the task of undercover with Lane and slained Vinter, the Bone Doctor alone. The scene on the bridge where Ilsa faught Gabriel was illogical with Ilsa holding a long sword and Gabriel holding only a small dagger. The movie did spend a lot of footage laying out Gabriel’s capabilities, yet Ilsa’s failure with her signature move was also illoogical because sword should have a natural advantage over a dagger.</p> <p>It’s not that I do not accept her death, it’s just that I am not satisfied with the way it happened. Even if they are going to let her die anyway as a result of Rebecca’s schedule, they could have made her death more dignified. I’m not saying that sacraficing herself for Grace’s survival is not worth it, it’s just the way they present it too scribbly. She could have died more heroically and the teammates could have shown more grief for her death.</p> <h3 id="the-introduction-of-peggy-carter-to-the-crew">The introduction of <em>Peggy Carter</em> to the crew</h3> <p>Talking about the replacement of Ilsa with Grace, our beloved Peggy Carter(Hayley Atwell’s role in Marvel Universe) was actually a good addition to the team from my perspective. The transformation of her character’s personality, though not perfectly smooth, was well articulated and it increased my expectations for her part in the upcoming Part 2.</p> <h3 id="the-formidable-ai">The formidable AI</h3> <p>I understand and awe the probabilistic model of artificial intelligence. By following its instructions and always taking the action which makes your desired result most likely, Gabriel could have been the most terrifying terrorist in this series. But AI is not unbreakable because any probabilistic prediction has the chance of not reflecting the actual result. I’m a little concerned because the movie did not do a good job of showing what the AI was capable of. Since nowadays almost everybody is familiar with the concept of AI, an ambiguous description of the AI might have been inadequate.</p> <h2 id="scenes">Scenes</h2> <h3 id="you-can-always-count-on-a-speeding-train">You can always count on a speeding train</h3> <p>What most people really like about a speeding train as the site for the grand finale is its relative closedness, isolation and high thrill, where the isolation makes it difficult to get support and the speed adds to the excitement. What’s more, the audience are able to enjoy more landscape as the train moving forward(towards uncertainty).</p> <h3 id="motorcycle-ride-off-a-cliff">Motorcycle ride off a cliff</h3> <p>Although intended as a selling point in the trailer, the actual visual perception of this scene is not comparable with the HALO jumping scene or freehand climbing <em>Burj Khalifa</em> tower scene in the previous movies. And perhaps because I did not chose the theater carefully(I casually chose a cinema where I worked without doing research) the fighting scene with Gabriel was also not comparable with that with Walker on the edge of a cliff.</p> <h3 id="the-poisonous-gas-bomb">The <em>poisonous</em> gas bomb</h3> <p>You remember the explosion of an apparant poisonous bomb filling the conference room with horrifying green gas in the trailer? With expectations of seeing who carried out such an attack and how he managed it but only to find that the man was Ethan and the bomb was merely anaesthetic, I was kind of disappointed for their well-conceived bluffing.</p> <h2 id="expectations-for-part-2">Expectations for Part 2</h2> <p>Upon finishing this blog, I browsed <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Mission_Impossible/">MI subreddit</a> for more discussions about Part 2. To put it simply, some wish Benji had been killed instead of Ilsa, some predict Ilsa would come back in the next movie, some quickly embrace Grace and never care about the bond between Ilsa and Ethan(and the whole team). I am open to any ending of this series and is optimistic about the performance of Grace, but it would be the best if they could let Ilsa back.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="reviews"/><category term="movies"/><category term="spoilers"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[freewheeling movie review on Tom Cruise's latest movie]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">my curriculum vitae</title><link href="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/resume/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="my curriculum vitae"/><published>2023-07-27T10:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-07-27T10:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/resume</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/resume/"><![CDATA[<p>Redirecting to my resume.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[my tech cv generated from chi-cv-template inspired by Alex Chi Z.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Self introduction for GAUnion</title><link href="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/self-intro-for-gaunion/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Self introduction for GAUnion"/><published>2023-07-12T15:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-07-12T15:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/self-intro-for-gaunion</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/self-intro-for-gaunion/"><![CDATA[<h1 id="self-introduction-for-gaunion-2024-recruitment">Self Introduction for GAUnion 2024 recruitment</h1> <h2 id="description">Description</h2> <p>Please write a short essay about yourself. In it, you should emphasize the <strong>distinct qualities</strong> or life experiences of yours which make you a good candidate for GAU and those for higher education abroad. And you would be advised and requested to give concrete and personal examples (Specific anecdotes are particularly welcome) to prove your claim (40%): (Please donot mention your id info, i.e. your name etc., so that the reviewers could evaluate the essay in a more objective manner)</p> <h2 id="essay">Essay</h2> <p>The characteristic treasured most by myself, if required to describe, is the courage of starting something entirely from scratch. Intelligence itself is a keen-edged sword, wielding properly, the owner could break through any obstacles ahead of him. But courage is more like a hammer, clumsy at first glance but the empowerment of which could accompany someone on the long trip of life.</p> <p>My recent wake-up time of life is almost the same time period last year as I am writting this essay this year, when students from my department were required to take the course <em>Lab Practice</em>, from the name of which you could know that it was a course aimed at those who want to conduct research. Unfortunately by that time I was not totally aware of my ability of carrying out research, so blindly choosing a research group and attend their weekly meetings became my only choice that seemed right. However, the experience was not beneficial to me because I could neither gain research inspirations nor accumulate technical skills from my lab. Even though I tried to understand how the research group was able to accomplish their tasks and pushed myself to catch up with the latest progress in the field, I was still not interested in the modern mathematical models of artificial intelligence. At first I thought the problem was not about research itself but my choice of researching field, yet after contacting other professors from systems track I realized that researching itself was not suitable for me whatever topic I chose. Last summer ended up miserable and fruitless and I only finished the course by doing chores.</p> <p>Adversity makes one think. Staring off as a student being encouraged to do scientifical research from the moment entering SJTU, I had not really thought about what it really means to do <strong>research</strong>, and what’s more important, my potentials about it. Yet research is not something that can be done by fleeting enthusiasm, it requires persistent devotions and ceaseless efforts. I realized I was not prepared for life like that and it was time to make some changes.</p> <p>Decision making was always harder. Like I mentioned above, since courage was my strength, I do not hesitate to put my ideas into action once my decision was made. In the field of computer science, one will never lack resources if you make your goals clearly. Starting 2022 Fall Semester, I quitted lab and started preparing for internships after finishing the regular coursework. My progress was slow at first, but better slow than never. Finally I was able to finish those course assignments with minimum effort and accumulated knowledge needed to start as an intern at my current company building their realtime transport network infrastructures. There is still a lot of uncertainty ahead but at least this summer my efforts will not be in vain.</p> <p>My motivation about going abroad for study emerged concurrently last summer as I was doing chores in my lab. Since my burden was not heavy, the fact that I spent a lot of time thinking and planning was imaginable. The original plan, SJTU’s plan for most of its students to be specific, for a student with passable grades like me without careful thinking and consideration was to fulfill Master or PhD degree within SJTU. Yet that route became unsuitable for me last summer because, to be frank, I no longer want to spend any more time on research based on experiences in my lab. Considering the domestic environment and atmosphere of pushing students to do research, I decided to finish my Master’s degree abroad. It was then that I realized I did not need to abide by any certain planning for students and started preparing my English examinations. Actually I took GRE tests that summer and then got my TOEFL score last winter. I love the feeling of being free and taking control of my own life.</p> <p>Back to the topic of the chatacteristic about starting something entirely from scratch. From the perspective of relationship building, going abroad for study is sort of an entire new start for every one of us. Unlike those who choose to finish advanced degrees within SJTU hence benefiting from the relasionship built in undergraduate years, we need to neglect the sunk cost with courage when making decisions and enbrace a fresh new start.</p> <p>I remember the old days when I was in junior high reading the Harry Potter series where the main characters go through the Sorting Ceremony when the Sorting Hat decides the House(i.e. department) they belong to. Unlike the main characters, I wished I had been suited for Ravenclaw instead of Gryffindor because I kind of hoped for more intelligence(so as to perform better in school) and underestimated the significance of courage. Only with time went by did I realize that I was more of a Gryffindor than a Ravenclaw. Even though an abstract name cannot summarize what kind of person I am, at least I hope I will never lack the courage to start something new.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="essays"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[gaunion 2024 recruitment essay]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">a post with bibliography</title><link href="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/post-bibliography/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="a post with bibliography"/><published>2023-07-12T13:56:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-07-12T13:56:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/post-bibliography</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/post-bibliography/"><![CDATA[<p>This post shows how to add bibliography to simple blog posts. If you would like something more academic, check the <a href="/blog/2021/distill/">distill style post</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="bib"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[an example of a blog post with bibliography]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">a post with jupyter notebook</title><link href="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/jupyter-notebook/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="a post with jupyter notebook"/><published>2023-07-04T12:57:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-07-04T12:57:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/jupyter-notebook</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/jupyter-notebook/"><![CDATA[<p>To include a jupyter notebook in a post, you can use the following code:</p> <div class="language-html highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code>{::nomarkdown}
{% assign jupyter_path = "assets/jupyter/blog.ipynb" | relative_url %}
{% capture notebook_exists %}{% file_exists assets/jupyter/blog.ipynb %}{% endcapture %}
{% if notebook_exists == "true" %}
    {% jupyter_notebook jupyter_path %}
{% else %}
    <span class="nt">&lt;p&gt;</span>Sorry, the notebook you are looking for does not exist.<span class="nt">&lt;/p&gt;</span>
{% endif %}
{:/nomarkdown}
</code></pre></div></div> <p>Let’s break it down: this is possible thanks to <a href="https://github.com/red-data-tools/jekyll-jupyter-notebook">Jekyll Jupyter Notebook plugin</a> that allows you to embed jupyter notebooks in your posts. It basically calls <a href="https://nbconvert.readthedocs.io/en/latest/usage.html#convert-html"><code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">jupyter nbconvert --to html</code></a> to convert the notebook to an html page and then includes it in the post. Since <a href="https://jekyllrb.com/docs/configuration/markdown/">Kramdown</a> is the default Markdown renderer for Jekyll, we need to surround the call to the plugin with the <a href="https://kramdown.gettalong.org/syntax.html#extensions">::nomarkdown</a> tag so that it stops processing this part with Kramdown and outputs the content as-is.</p> <p>The plugin takes as input the path to the notebook, but it assumes the file exists. If you want to check if the file exists before calling the plugin, you can use the <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">file_exists</code> filter. This avoids getting a 404 error from the plugin and ending up displaying the main page inside of it instead. If the file does not exist, you can output a message to the user. The code displayed above outputs the following:</p> <div class="jupyter-notebook" style="position: relative; width: 100%; margin: 0 auto;"> <div class="jupyter-notebook-iframe-container"> <iframe src="/assets/jupyter/blog.ipynb.html" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; border-style: none;" width="100%" height="100%" onload="this.parentElement.style.paddingBottom = (this.contentWindow.document.documentElement.scrollHeight + 10) + 'px'"></iframe> </div> </div> <p>Note that the jupyter notebook supports both light and dark themes.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="jupyter"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[an example of a blog post with jupyter notebook]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">a post with custom blockquotes</title><link href="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/custom-blockquotes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="a post with custom blockquotes"/><published>2023-05-12T19:53:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-05-12T19:53:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/custom-blockquotes</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/custom-blockquotes/"><![CDATA[<p>This post shows how to add custom styles for blockquotes. Based on <a href="https://github.com/sighingnow/jekyll-gitbook">jekyll-gitbook</a> implementation.</p> <p>We decided to support the same custom blockquotes as in <a href="https://sighingnow.github.io/jekyll-gitbook/jekyll/2022-06-30-tips_warnings_dangers.html">jekyll-gitbook</a>, which are also found in a lot of other sites’ styles. The styles definitions can be found on the <a href="https://github.com/alshedivat/al-folio/blob/master/_sass/_base.scss">_base.scss</a> file, more specifically:</p> <div class="language-scss highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="cm">/* Tips, warnings, and dangers */</span>
<span class="nc">.post</span> <span class="nc">.post-content</span> <span class="nt">blockquote</span> <span class="p">{</span>
    <span class="k">&amp;</span><span class="nc">.block-tip</span> <span class="p">{</span>
    <span class="nl">border-color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-tip-block</span><span class="p">);</span>
    <span class="nl">background-color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-tip-block-bg</span><span class="p">);</span>

    <span class="nt">p</span> <span class="p">{</span>
      <span class="nl">color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-tip-block-text</span><span class="p">);</span>
    <span class="p">}</span>

    <span class="nt">h1</span><span class="o">,</span> <span class="nt">h2</span><span class="o">,</span> <span class="nt">h3</span><span class="o">,</span> <span class="nt">h4</span><span class="o">,</span> <span class="nt">h5</span><span class="o">,</span> <span class="nt">h6</span> <span class="p">{</span>
      <span class="nl">color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-tip-block-title</span><span class="p">);</span>
    <span class="p">}</span>
  <span class="p">}</span>

  <span class="k">&amp;</span><span class="nc">.block-warning</span> <span class="p">{</span>
    <span class="nl">border-color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-warning-block</span><span class="p">);</span>
    <span class="nl">background-color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-warning-block-bg</span><span class="p">);</span>

    <span class="nt">p</span> <span class="p">{</span>
      <span class="nl">color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-warning-block-text</span><span class="p">);</span>
    <span class="p">}</span>

    <span class="nt">h1</span><span class="o">,</span> <span class="nt">h2</span><span class="o">,</span> <span class="nt">h3</span><span class="o">,</span> <span class="nt">h4</span><span class="o">,</span> <span class="nt">h5</span><span class="o">,</span> <span class="nt">h6</span> <span class="p">{</span>
      <span class="nl">color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-warning-block-title</span><span class="p">);</span>
    <span class="p">}</span>
  <span class="p">}</span>

  <span class="k">&amp;</span><span class="nc">.block-danger</span> <span class="p">{</span>
    <span class="nl">border-color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-danger-block</span><span class="p">);</span>
    <span class="nl">background-color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-danger-block-bg</span><span class="p">);</span>

    <span class="nt">p</span> <span class="p">{</span>
      <span class="nl">color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-danger-block-text</span><span class="p">);</span>
    <span class="p">}</span>

    <span class="nt">h1</span><span class="o">,</span> <span class="nt">h2</span><span class="o">,</span> <span class="nt">h3</span><span class="o">,</span> <span class="nt">h4</span><span class="o">,</span> <span class="nt">h5</span><span class="o">,</span> <span class="nt">h6</span> <span class="p">{</span>
      <span class="nl">color</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="nf">var</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="o">--</span><span class="n">global-danger-block-title</span><span class="p">);</span>
    <span class="p">}</span>
  <span class="p">}</span>
<span class="p">}</span>
</code></pre></div></div> <p>A regular blockquote can be used as following:</p> <div class="language-markdown highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="gt">&gt; This is a regular blockquote</span>
<span class="gt">&gt; and it can be used as usual</span>
</code></pre></div></div> <blockquote> <p>This is a regular blockquote and it can be used as usual</p> </blockquote> <p>These custom styles can be used by adding the specific class to the blockquote, as follows:</p> <div class="language-markdown highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="gt">&gt; ##### TIP</span>
<span class="gt">&gt;</span>
<span class="gt">&gt; A tip can be used when you want to give advice</span>
<span class="gt">&gt; related to a certain content.</span>
{: .block-tip }
</code></pre></div></div> <blockquote class="block-tip"> <h5 id="tip">TIP</h5> <p>A tip can be used when you want to give advice related to a certain content.</p> </blockquote> <div class="language-markdown highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="gt">&gt; ##### WARNING</span>
<span class="gt">&gt;</span>
<span class="gt">&gt; This is a warning, and thus should</span>
<span class="gt">&gt; be used when you want to warn the user</span>
{: .block-warning }
</code></pre></div></div> <blockquote class="block-warning"> <h5 id="warning">WARNING</h5> <p>This is a warning, and thus should be used when you want to warn the user</p> </blockquote> <div class="language-markdown highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="gt">&gt; ##### DANGER</span>
<span class="gt">&gt;</span>
<span class="gt">&gt; This is a danger zone, and thus should</span>
<span class="gt">&gt; be used carefully</span>
{: .block-danger }
</code></pre></div></div> <blockquote class="block-danger"> <h5 id="danger">DANGER</h5> <p>This is a danger zone, and thus should be used carefully</p> </blockquote>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="blockquotes"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[an example of a blog post with custom blockquotes]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">a post with table of contents on a sidebar</title><link href="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/sidebar-table-of-contents/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="a post with table of contents on a sidebar"/><published>2023-04-25T14:14:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-04-25T14:14:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/sidebar-table-of-contents</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/sidebar-table-of-contents/"><![CDATA[<p>This post shows how to add a table of contents as a sidebar.</p> <h2 id="adding-a-table-of-contents">Adding a Table of Contents</h2> <p>To add a table of contents to a post as a sidebar, simply add</p> <div class="language-yml highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="na">toc</span><span class="pi">:</span>
  <span class="na">sidebar</span><span class="pi">:</span> <span class="s">left</span>
</code></pre></div></div> <p>to the front matter of the post. The table of contents will be automatically generated from the headings in the post. If you wish to display the sidebar to the right, simply change <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">left</code> to <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">right</code>.</p> <h3 id="example-of-sub-heading-1">Example of Sub-Heading 1</h3> <p>Jean shorts raw denim Vice normcore, art party High Life PBR skateboard stumptown vinyl kitsch. Four loko meh 8-bit, tousled banh mi tilde forage Schlitz dreamcatcher twee 3 wolf moon. Chambray asymmetrical paleo salvia, sartorial umami four loko master cleanse drinking vinegar brunch. <a href="https://www.pinterest.com">Pinterest</a> DIY authentic Schlitz, hoodie Intelligentsia butcher trust fund brunch shabby chic Kickstarter forage flexitarian. Direct trade <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cold-pressed_juice">cold-pressed</a> meggings stumptown plaid, pop-up taxidermy. Hoodie XOXO fingerstache scenester Echo Park. Plaid ugh Wes Anderson, freegan pug selvage fanny pack leggings pickled food truck DIY irony Banksy.</p> <h3 id="example-of-another-sub-heading-1">Example of another Sub-Heading 1</h3> <p>Jean shorts raw denim Vice normcore, art party High Life PBR skateboard stumptown vinyl kitsch. Four loko meh 8-bit, tousled banh mi tilde forage Schlitz dreamcatcher twee 3 wolf moon. Chambray asymmetrical paleo salvia, sartorial umami four loko master cleanse drinking vinegar brunch. <a href="https://www.pinterest.com">Pinterest</a> DIY authentic Schlitz, hoodie Intelligentsia butcher trust fund brunch shabby chic Kickstarter forage flexitarian. Direct trade <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cold-pressed_juice">cold-pressed</a> meggings stumptown plaid, pop-up taxidermy. Hoodie XOXO fingerstache scenester Echo Park. Plaid ugh Wes Anderson, freegan pug selvage fanny pack leggings pickled food truck DIY irony Banksy.</p> <h2 data-toc-text="Customizing" id="customizing-your-table-of-contents">Customizing Your Table of Contents</h2> <p>If you want to learn more about how to customize the table of contents of your sidebar, you can check the <a href="https://afeld.github.io/bootstrap-toc/">bootstrap-toc</a> documentation. Notice that you can even customize the text of the heading that will be displayed on the sidebar.</p> <h3 id="example-of-sub-heading-2">Example of Sub-Heading 2</h3> <p>Jean shorts raw denim Vice normcore, art party High Life PBR skateboard stumptown vinyl kitsch. Four loko meh 8-bit, tousled banh mi tilde forage Schlitz dreamcatcher twee 3 wolf moon. Chambray asymmetrical paleo salvia, sartorial umami four loko master cleanse drinking vinegar brunch. <a href="https://www.pinterest.com">Pinterest</a> DIY authentic Schlitz, hoodie Intelligentsia butcher trust fund brunch shabby chic Kickstarter forage flexitarian. Direct trade <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cold-pressed_juice">cold-pressed</a> meggings stumptown plaid, pop-up taxidermy. Hoodie XOXO fingerstache scenester Echo Park. Plaid ugh Wes Anderson, freegan pug selvage fanny pack leggings pickled food truck DIY irony Banksy.</p> <h3 id="example-of-another-sub-heading-2">Example of another Sub-Heading 2</h3> <p>Jean shorts raw denim Vice normcore, art party High Life PBR skateboard stumptown vinyl kitsch. Four loko meh 8-bit, tousled banh mi tilde forage Schlitz dreamcatcher twee 3 wolf moon. Chambray asymmetrical paleo salvia, sartorial umami four loko master cleanse drinking vinegar brunch. <a href="https://www.pinterest.com">Pinterest</a> DIY authentic Schlitz, hoodie Intelligentsia butcher trust fund brunch shabby chic Kickstarter forage flexitarian. Direct trade <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cold-pressed_juice">cold-pressed</a> meggings stumptown plaid, pop-up taxidermy. Hoodie XOXO fingerstache scenester Echo Park. Plaid ugh Wes Anderson, freegan pug selvage fanny pack leggings pickled food truck DIY irony Banksy.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="toc"/><category term="sidebar"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[an example of a blog post with table of contents on a sidebar]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">a post with audios</title><link href="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/audios/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="a post with audios"/><published>2023-04-25T10:25:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-04-25T10:25:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/audios</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sylvansun.github.io/blog/2023/audios/"><![CDATA[<p>This is an example post with audios. It supports local audio files.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <audio src="/assets/audio/epicaly-short-113909.mp3" controls=""/> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <audio src="https://cdn.pixabay.com/download/audio/2022/06/25/audio_69a61cd6d6.mp3" controls=""/> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> A simple, elegant caption looks good between video rows, after each row, or doesn't have to be there at all. </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="audios"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[this is what included audios could look like]]></summary></entry></feed>